Contact Details:

Date of Birth: November 22nd 1969

Marital Status: SingleNationality: Jordanian

• Contact numbers: +962-79-906 1026

• E-mail address: naji.abdulghani@gmail.com



Objective:

To improve and utilize my passion and skills of customer service, sales & marketing which is backed up with my diversified experience at the hospitality industry and customers service.

My aim is to be an active team player on a management level within a professional work environment in a leading hotel group, hotel owners, or a service oriented organization whereby, I can add up to my experience and progress in my career with no limits.

My hard and smart work approach, dedication and creativity, entitles me to proactively contribute to the success of the company.

Work Experience:

January 2008- present

KEMPINSKI HOTEL ISHTAR DEAD SEA

- Guest Relations Manager (2008 2009)
- Asst. Front Office Manager (2009 2011)
- Groups & Sales Events Manager /In-Charge for the Events Department (2011 2013)
- Director of Groups & Events (2013 2015)
- Director of Weddings & Social Events (Nov. 2015 2017)
- Cluster Director of Weddings & Social Events (2017 Present)

The Cluster Director of Weddings & Social Events will drive the social events to reach pre-set goals, mission & expectations, expand client database, maximize revenue opportunities, build a strong presence in the events and will serve as an ambassador to promote leadership directed towards sales growth, direct all functions according to the offered services whilst adhering to the utmost level of service excellence with both existing and new clients.

I joined this resort allowing, me to work once again in the field I like working in taking care of guests and their needs. I am in charge of running this department at this 5 stars + resort. I put all of the operating procedures together allowing maximum customer satisfaction and increasing sales. Below are some of my tasks

- 1. Interview and select job applicants, train and supervise staff in the performance of their duties; conduct performance appraisals and discipline employees.
- 2. Maintain an absolute confidential and professional driven work environment.
- 3. Responsible for directing the entire operations of the events team.
- 4. Accountable for long & short team planning for social events.
- 5. Responsible for establishing & monitoring measurable goals for the divisions.
- 6. Responsible for developing & implementing business plan & long term strategy for the successful growth of the division.
- 7. Participate & conduct regular briefings for the division team.
- 8. Maintain quality standards & service excellence within the division.
- 9. Conceive, develop & implement creative sales, marketing & public relations strategies & tactics that support & enhance organizational goals.
- 10. Implement & utilizes professional sales skills & practices to empower the team to maximize generates qualified leads, participate in professional networking opportunities to enhance awareness within the community and develop a strong client database.
- 11. Ensure maximum revenue generation for the functions & responsible to facilitate achieving set targets.
- 12. Responsible in creating an appropriate identity in the local market & implementing marketing strategies, best practices & campaigns to guarantee the success of set goals.
- 13. Anticipate & ensure the through fulfillment of client requirements & expectations as outlined in the events orders.
- 14. Ensure the correct planning, organization, & execution of functions that meet the standards & expectations of clients & the Hotel in relation to client communication and liaison with the needed in-house responsible departments & outsourced related vendors, contracting process, catering services & any related responsibility.
- 15. Provide professional advice & guidance to assist the function clients with any aspect of their wedding for as follows:
 - Provide expert advice & professional suggestions.
 - Coordinate & Liaison.
 - Communicate Successfully.
 - Assist & guide function clients.
 - Find creative solutions.
 - De-stress & calm function clients.
 - Planning & organization.
 - Build strong working relations with industry leading suppliers/vendors.
 - Stay up to date with new industry trends & best practices, constant update on direct competition.
- 16. Ensure division is working within allocated budget & manage expenses within budget constraints & according to revenue.
- 17. Perform other assigned duties that contribute to the Hotel's mission & objective.

July 2005- December 2007

FOSTER GROUP REGIONAL OFFICE - AMMAN

Personal Assistant – President

I joined this company. In my new capacity, and besides to managing all business and personal related issues of the president, I take care of all the companies executive Directors travel and lodging arrangements. The Company's president, Mrs. Foster was a permanent guest in the Four Seasons hotel in Amman and I was asked to join her office.

The company is involved in Rebuilding Iraq, in Power generation and supply projects; and has several projects in Gulf countries as well as in Jordan. I look after two more satellite office in Dubai and Kuwait.

2002 - June 2005

FOUR SEASONS HOTEL - AMMAN

Concierge Manager

Duties:

- 1. Interview and select job applicants, train and supervise staff in the performance of their duties; conduct performance appraisals and discipline employees.
- 2. Schedule all Concierge staff to ensure maximum guest satisfaction within budgeted guidelines. Complete all payroll records required and prepare labor forecast.
- 3. knowledge on what activities are available in the city, i.e. theater, the arts, special exhibits, concerts, shows, sports, leisure activities, sightseeing tours, etc. and to establish close contacts with people in these areas to provide information, ticketing, reservations, etc. for guests.
- 4. Perform all reasonable services a guest may require, anticipate guest requests and requirements in order to satisfy them efficiently and promptly.
- 5. Ensure the proper handling of guest messages, mail, faxes, telexes, packages, flowers, etc.
- 6. Work closely with the Valet Parking Department to ensure the smooth handling of guest and patron vehicles; closely oversee the door and bell staff to ensure the efficient handling of guest luggage.
- 7. Work closely with the Front Office staff in the handling of groups, VIPs, repeat guests, etc. Establishes rapport with frequent visitors; keeps Reservations and Front Office staff well-informed about guests' preferences.
- 8. Work closely with the Director of Housekeeping and the Chief Engineer to rectify problems in guest rooms.
- 9. Resolve guest complaints in conjunction with the Assistant Managers, keeping senior management well informed as to the problems and actions taken.
- 10. Respond properly in any hotel emergency or safety situation.
- 11. Perform other tasks or projects as assigned by hotel management and staff.

2002 - 2002

GRAND HYATT - AMMAN

Front Desk Agent

- 1. Executing the day to day basic work process of the Front office, such as reservations, receptionist, check ins/check outs and guest's escorts to their room.
- 2. Present regular reports on my duties and front office issues to the front office manager
- 3. Assist the concierge desk team whenever the work requires so.

1998 - February 2002

MARRIOT WORLDWIDE SALES OFFICE & RESERVATION CENTER (AMMAN and DUBAI)

Marriott Rewards and Customer Service Supervisor – Middle East

- 1. Preparing and conducting presentations for the Marriott Rewards Program.
- 2. Handling customer services issues
- 3. Handling International Marriott hotels reservations
- 4. Checking status of membership cards for Marriott Rewards Customers.
- 5. Acting as Worldwide reservation manager in absences of the reservation manager.
- 6. Conducting training sessions to new and old employees of the center.
- 7. Helping in and attending other inquiries from Marriott Middle East properties and general sales offices.
- 8. Presenting the sales and other Marriott rewards reports on a monthly basis to the head office in Omaha USA
- 9. Conducting sales calls to promote Marriott hotels around the world.
- 10. Issuing points certificates for Marriott rewards bookings.

1997 - 1998

MARRIOTT GENERAL SALES OFFICE, RIYADH-SAUDI ARABIA

Sales Manager

- 1. Conducting Sales calls to promote Marriott Hotels around the world
- 2. Issuing Marriott prepaid vouchers for bookings
- 3. Planning offer for sub-agents on an agreement rate basis.
- 4. Preparing and conducting presentations on newly opened Marriott branches around the world to travel agents.
- 5. Training the sales team on proper customer's approach, sales calls and service.
- 6. Supervise designing flyers that update the customers with any special offers in any Marriott branch around the world.

1994 - 1997

AL QASR HOTEL - AMMAN

Front Office Manager

- 1. Checking in/Out customers and handling their requirements.
- 2. Making reservations
- 3. Conducting sales calls to travel agents & key accounts
- 4. Conducting training sessions to the new employees
- 5. Presenting room revenue reports to the General Manager on weekly and monthly basis.

Education:

- 1994 Front Office Skills
- Maple Leaf Center Amman
- 1992 Computer Skills
- Arabic Society College Amman
- 1990 High School Diploma
- Al-Jamil High School Kuwait

Skills:

- Good computer skills.
- Fidelio & Opera
- Marsha
- Excellent in Arabic & English languages both written & spoken.

Training Courses:

- GHA.com
- The management behind our management
- My Guest My Customer Workshop
- Basic Sales & Hospitality Workshop
- Guest Courtesy Training
- Supervisory Development Program
- Finance for Non Financials
- New Manager Orientation
- Becoming a Global Manager
- Conflict Resolution.
- Behavior Based Interviewing.
- Delegation, Time Management & Organizational Skills.
- Coaching your team of individuals.
- Managing & Reviewing Performance.
- Harassment in the Work place.

- Complaint Handling.
- Glitch logy.
- One Minute Manager.
- How to run Successful Meetings.
- The Why & How behind FS Mgt.
- Goal Settings.
- Standard Stars.
- Telephone Etiquette.

Interests:

Traveling, Swimming and Horse riding

References:

> Mr. Sebastien Mariette

General Manager - Kempinski Hotels - Dubai / UAE

E-mail: Sebastien.Mariette@kempinski.com

Mr. Mohammed Saed

Cluster Director of Sales & Marketing - Kempinski Ishtar Dead Sea & Aqaba

E-mail: Mohammed.Saed@kempinski.com

Mr. Kees Heuveling

General Manager - Kempinski Hotels & Resorts

E-mail: Kees.Heuveling@kempinski.com

> Mr. Masami Egami

General Manager - Kempinski Hotels & Resorts

E-mail: Masami.Egami@kempinski.com